MY BELOVED DEMON
FINANCIAL HEAD OF THE GROUP MR. CHA
FOUND HANGING IN THE DRESSING ROOM
Jung Koo Won?
You have something very dear to me.
I want you to be more responsible.
Acid?
You…
It didn't occur to me then.
What…
are you like that
I…
the demon
You people call me…
the devil
EPISODE 3
JOIN FORCES WITH THE DEMON
We analyzed the liquid on the ground,
and it turned out to be sulfuric acid.
If so much acid of such concentration
hit your face
she would melt it and you would die.
It is likely that you are a target.
Do you suspect anyone?
I Cha Tae Chun,
head of the financial department of Mire Group.
I am calling to inform you of important information.
Does anyone remember?
No.
I can't remember anyone
who would hate me enough for that.
People are so insignificant.
come in
go
Line up here.
Quick!
Are homeless people allowed in casinos now?
They have bad business.
Where do you think you are?
Ahead! You can't do that with a woman!
If you are in such a hurry, I will question you first.
Sit down, everyone.
sit down
What is your ID card number?
Drink this while you wait, sir.
I don't drink that kind of slop.
You with your contempt.
Did you live abroad or something?
Get it right.
I'm older than I look.
Of course. Okay, fine.
VERIFICATION OF PERSONAL DATA
Her name means "lady".
NAME: NO SUK NYO
ADDRESS: UNKNOWN
Why is To To Hee taking so long?
What the hell?
A wonderful aroma of Arabica.
Now you can barely hold on.
You can actually die.
And very...
in a minor way.
Why are there so many crazy people now?
Did you finish?
Did you expect her?
Probably, his presence is reassuring.
Please keep us posted on progress.
Good. Get home safely.
do not think
what should they do?
I highly doubt it.
The roulette wheel is finally spinning.
- Roulette?
- Yes.
I bet everything on an odd number.
Is it so hard to stay safe?
What if I was even a moment late?
My precious tattoo would burn.
So you say you are a demon?
You are the devil.
Why call yourself a demon?
Are you a pokemon?
Poke…
Listen carefully.
A demon is an extremely noble being,
whose purpose is to make deals with people.
What are the deals?
To put it simply, I fulfill people's wishes.
- Like a genie from a lamp?
- Don't compare me to a chubby smurf.
You have seen what I am capable of.
If I'm not a demon, then who am I?
We usually call such
like you superhumans.
Forget it. Think what you want.
- Then you are definitely a genie from...
- Besides that.
to be honest
I don't care if you're a devil or an angel.
- You don't believe me.
- That's not the point.
The point is that you own it
amazing powers
and that I have your dad
which is the source of them all.
Then you don't believe.
No.
I knew that.
You people are forever in doubt.
And I was interested in
why are you so obsessed with your tat?
It must have been difficult for you.
You should be by my side
to use forces
but you have no reason for it.
You are not my ex, not that you are not a boyfriend.
It seems that you need it now
a reason that will give you
the right to be near me.
- I'm wrong.
- What are you trying to say?
We share the same fate.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Same fate?
We are now in the same boat.
There is a way for both of us to win in this situation.
Which one exactly?
You will be my bodyguard.
A bodyguard? What are you talking about?
Let me explain to you in detail.
A security guard is a person
which protects the client…
I know what a security guard does.
I am a demon.
You tell me to protect
some insignificant person?
You can tell yourself
that you protect instead
your precious tattoo.
- No.
- If you don't want to protect,
watch out for the fight against the villains.
Do you want me to fight for you?
Do you really think I'm a pokemon?
You'll be in trouble if I die, right?
What will happen to my dad if I die?
As you know
now i'm in danger
I don't know who is hunting me and why
but someone wants to kill me.
you need your tattoo
and I need your strength.
It's the only way we both get what we want.
Do not agree?
- Will you be my bodyguard?
- My answer is a firm no.
What do you offer? Do you have a better idea?
I don't know, but I won't be your bodyguard.
- Where are you?
- That scoundrel can try again.
I'll take you to the door.
That's what a security guard does.
It's not too difficult.
I say that I will never be your bodyguard.
Stand before me. I'll cover your back.
What is the security here?
Can't you hear yourself?
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
I'm amazing at how…
Oh, I'm sorry.
Maybe not.
Just think:
my amazing powers depend on my wrist
such an insignificant and weak person.
If he breaks into her home?
If she dies, I'll lose my strength forever
how do I make deals then?
So be her guardian,
if you are so worried.
don't make me laugh
How can a demon become a guardian?
Demons were guardians.
What kind of delusion is this?
DEMONS FIRST
EXISTED AMONG PEOPLE
AND PROTECTED THEM AS GUARDIANS
Keepers are actually guards.
I don't want to be either.
I was made to be a demon.
How did you even get it?
I was cleaning your table.
by the way
what if To To Hee gets confused about who you are?
She doesn't even believe I'm a demon.
And you know what people are like.
I saw the devil.
- Just a little.
- Lord.
What did the devil look like?
The devil appeared before me
in the image of the man of my dreams,
to tempt my soul.
Turned proportionate nose.
Porcelain-smooth skin.
Sexy but innocent lips.
And most importantly,
he had a melancholy look.
Even his voice was music to me.
In the end I am
fell in love with the devil.
No one will believe that I exist
and soon everyone will forget
that they have heard about me at all.
You are right.
In a past life, I was well beaten
for saying he saw an evil spirit.
My buttocks still hurt when it rains.
You exaggerate.
It wasn't even in this life.
Then my strength will really disappear,
if To To Hee dies?
I don't mind. That's why I'm so nervous.
Something bad could happen.
That damn instruction is full of threats
and no useful information.
You should just throw it away and...
No, it's not worth it.
Do you recognize this as an instruction?
I just want to give back
his peaceful and comfortable life.
I just want to live forever
flawless predator,
that never ages or dies.
Am I asking too much?
- You won't hide it?
- You will find it anyway.
I really enjoy the challenge.
Seriously…
Be my bodyguard.
How annoying.
Should I go get laser tattoo removal?
Is she threatening a demon now?
I booked a laser.
Removal will begin in five, four,
three, two, one.
- I killed Pororo's tattoo.
- She's crazy!
She's so crazy
PHOTO SENT
He doesn't bite.
He saved me again.
Like last time.
Mr. Cha, Head of Finance of Mire Group
accused of misappropriation of money,
was found dead during the day.
A passer-by found his body
in a public toilet near his house
and reported about it around 2:00 p.m.
MY GENTLE FLOWER
Why are you so clingy?
You saw me only a day ago.
I know you are happy to call me.
Are you calling to boil me down?
That's not why I'm calling.
Is everything okay in your company now?
In my company?
And what?
I saw on the news
that your head of finance has hanged himself.
The thing is that he is mine
called yesterday and said
that he has important information.
I neglected it
I thought he just wanted money.
But after his suicide
it seems to me that something is wrong.
And you should not worry
about your own company?
It's empty.
Then blow your nose
and focus on your company.
Mrs. Yun.
Bring me all the articles
about the deceased financial head
and financial statements for the last ten years
and for headquarters,
and for subsidiaries.
All this time I was blind.
Good morning, Director Chong.
come in
You seem to be in a good mood today.
I just realized
maybe the situation is not too bad.
My dad hasn't disappeared.
It is safe on that woman's wrist.
You are a positive person.
And I realized
that I couldn't get my dad back
- by a simple jump into the water.
- And what?
The conditions must be the same,
like when i lost him
What are the conditions?
Location, temperature, water, etc.
If the conditions are the same,
I will definitely get my tattoo back.
It is logical.
Do you smell burning?
I roasted the coffee beans to perfection today.
That's not the point.
It's the smell of burning meat, not plants.
You are right.
Smells like grilling a steak.
And I feel the heat.
- Mr. Pak.
- What?
What…
- Is it spontaneous combustion?
- Just like that?
You got your dad back…
What is going on here?
Did you tell her everything? why you…
My life was in danger.
I had to confess.
Help us here!
It gets worse!
Is the flame fueled by oxygen?
The years of scientific delusion!
Hot as hell!
Hot!
What just happened?
Spontaneous ignition has begun.
No, not everything is fine.
I just fell asleep.
Who calls so early?
SAVIOR KU WON
Will you be my bodyguard?
- She answered.
- Quiet. I hear
where are you At home?
Yes.
We have to see each other. I will come right away.
What is your plan?
I have a deal to make.
Put everything! I have to go immediately!
Immediately?
A little
You can't just show up.
I didn't even wash.
I will be your bodyguard.
Really?
Ok, you made the right…
Hold on. What made you change your mind?
You were so against it yesterday.
I thought about it all night
and suddenly realized.
Even minor things must be protected.
People even protect the insignificant
and unnecessary insects,
like barbel beetles.
Are you comparing me to a weevil?
You both need protection.
Something is suspicious here.
There must be a reason why you changed your mind.
Yesterday, the idea caused a stir.
What made you…
- What are you doing?
- What?
Very suspicious.
You are probably hiding...
Focus, To To Hee.
We have one destiny, haven't we forgotten?
Never forget that we are in the same boat.
You are right.
Of course, be my bodyguard.
Can you start today?
But first
you must come with me.
This place…
It's too high here!
Why did you bring me here?
People can be seen best here
with whom an agreement can be concluded.
I'm afraid of heights!
Oh, go away!
Found it! Ahead!
Here.
Let me drink.
can you hold
Additional chemotherapy does not make sense.
However...
Can we try something?
Sorry.
There.
I'm not even asking you to let her live.
I only ask
so that Yoon Seo would not suffer anymore.
At least for one day.
That's all I want.
I will fulfill your wish.
who are you
I am a demon.
In other words,
you just got crazy lucky.
What?
If you sign an agreement with me,
your child will live ten years.
i don't know who you are
but you can't just invade here...
Yoon Seo!
Oh no!
- We both have little time, that's how.
- Yoon Seo...
How do you…
The conditions are simple.
In ten years you will go to hell.
If I get
Will Yoon Seo really be able to live?
Decide before I find another person.
Wait, you're putting too much pressure on her…
Do not climb.
Let her think. This is a difficult decision.
No time!
Time?
You do it because...
I will sign.
I will go not only to hell,
if it would end Yoon Seo's suffering.
It almost didn't work.
Spontaneous ignition is accelerated,
what more do I use my powers?
Do you know where to buy a nice cake?
After all, this is your industry.
Pie?
I always celebrate a new deal with dessert.
What will happen if the fire engulfs you?
i will burn
So you will die?
Something like that.
I will cease to exist forever
and this is crueler than death.
So that's why you make deals.
So as not to burn.
And even celebrate with a cake.
You really are the devil, aren't you?
In the world, you have to pay for everything.
I will live forever for
that I will fulfill people's wishes.
I think it's worth celebrating.
You exploit people's misfortunes.
Is that bad?
You also want to do it with me.
Every moment of your life
built on the despair and misfortune of others.
Doesn't that bother you?
I don't know what got you so upset
but I save people.
Have you not seen a child die in agony?
And she will be happy
when she finds out that she survived
at the expense of a dear person?
You probably won't be able to understand it,
but people are capable of feeling
the so-called guilt.
People often romanticize
unnecessary and ineffective emotions
as a component of humanity.
Let's go to the office.
No.
I will not use you
so as not to exploit the misfortunes of others.
You can say it now.
But when life is in danger,
then you will rely on my strength.
By nature, humans are worse than demons,
when it comes to selfishness.
Apart from all the dirty tricks
also murder?
You will have to pay
for what has been done
That's what I'm talking about.
Director Chong! how are your fingers
I signed the agreement
and the fingers are fine.
It's time to talk to me.
I was terribly worried
I thought we would never see each other again.
Who do you think I am?
I was worried when you took off
so i investigated the day
when you lost your dad
- And?
- Listen.
Based on the assumption that you fell into the sea
30 minutes after midnight,
sea water temperature
it was 15.8 degrees Celsius there.
And then the most important thing.
that night
the moon was full.
How often do they happen?
Every 29.5 days.
Since 1.5 days have passed…
Only 28 days left.
28 more days?
It's too long.
But aren't you To To Hee's bodyguard now?
Oh, about that.
- I was fired.
- Already?
She doesn't want my help anymore.
Did you have a fight or something?
- People are just too greedy!
- What?
Why do they pray
if they don't want to pay?
I didn't hear a word.
Like they're bothering me
that I may perform miracles in vain.
Now that I literally
extinguished that fire
everything became the opposite.
What exactly did she say?
Equally.
I don't care what she says now.
In response to a recent
scandal with sugar in juice
the PR department suggests focusing
on new healthy products.
Mrs?
Mrs. To.
Please continue.
A healthy image of our new products
will replace all negativity
from the sugar in juice scandal.
"Defend yourself..."
That is: "Attack."
Your words inspired me.
I brought what you asked for.
And I will hire bodyguards for you as soon as possible.
And she will be happy,
when she finds out that she survived
at the expense of a dear person?
You probably won't be able to understand it,
but people are capable of feeling
the so-called guilt.
Is something bothering you?
Absolutely not. Why should I worry?
"SEUL HANSE" MEDICAL CENTER
Oh no.
I'm sorry, sir.
Tell him you're sorry, Yoon Seo.
Sorry.
So your name is Yoon So?
Do you have a wish?
Her wish will now come true.
She wanted to spend
tenth birthday outside the hospital.
Did you want that?
Birthday outside the hospital?
No? So what is your wish?
I hope the parents
will not suffer because of me.
Here is my wish.
Yoon Seo.
Beloved.
Mom!
- Don't run, you'll get caught.
- Don't run, Yun Seo.
A little
I told you not to run.
People.
They are forever so complicated.
Interest in Korean food is at its peak now.
Korean food is already famous.
Now it's time to celebrate the drinks and pastries.
So in…
The cake has arrived.
- Thank you.
- Delicious.
- How many candles are there?
- Ten.
You're ten, Yoon Seo.
- You like flowers, right?
- I'm sorry.
- Let's sing.
- Okay.
That's it.
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Yoon So
- Happy birthday, Yoon So's dear
- Happy birthday to you
I will go not only to hell,
if it ends Yoon Seo's suffering.
We have arrived, ladies.
Agov.
That is, Mrs.
Do you have a weapon? Maybe a gun?
MARTIAL ARTS FOR GUARDS
It looks like…
I don't need him too much,
because I myself am a weapon.
UNDERSTANDING PROTECTIVE EQUIPMENT
Mr. Khan.
Why suddenly a security guard?
Mrs. To will be in the center
our promotion of new products.
Probably preparing for the glory that will come.
She really is one step ahead of everyone else, isn't she?
By the way, do not think
that the guard is inappropriately handsome?
That is, how is it "improper"?
Here are bonuses for employees.
Since he is a bodyguard,
he must be a great fighter.
He's perfect, right?
But I bet he has a weakness.
- Must have.
- That's right.
- For example...
Maybe he's weak in bed.
Why is this a weakness?
How can that be a fault?
This is completely normal!
It can happen to anyone.
Why might this be a problem?
I didn't want to know.
Being a security guard is quite simple.
Were you expecting some drama?
Absolutely not.
why did you come back
You didn't want to be my bodyguard.
Just like that.
My life was so peaceful
and perfect, which became almost boring.
I thought a little trouble wouldn't hurt.
But what made you change your mind?
You didn't want my power.
Just like that.
Only a scoundrel will deal with a scoundrel.
How did you become a demon?
Were you born with it?
It's a family affair
like a family run restaurant?
Comparing demons to restaurants?
I don't know what…
The language was simply taken away.
How old are you? when were you born
I lived as a demon for 200 years.
You really do look much younger.
So that means there was a time
when were you not a demon?
- I was a person.
- Yes?
Of course I was on another level
compared to the rest of the insignificant people.
But I don't remember that.
I think it's self-hatred.
You think people are insignificant
because they themselves were human.
So it is written in the book.
"God had to
for someone to work in hell
therefore he personally chose a person
to make a demon."
I am the person he chose.
Not because you were special
and because they met the requirements of the job.
You are a scoundrel.
WORDS OF ALMIGHTY CHU:
ENOUGH OF ME. I LOVE YOU SO HEE
What is it now?
ALMIGHTY CHU
The dialed number is not available.
- Turn the car around.
- Leave a message…
Mrs. Chu?
Why are you sitting on the floor?
It will hurt your knee.
I can't believe my eyes.
Mrs. Chu?
MISSED CALLS
FROM MY GENTLE FLOWER
Ms. Chu, are you all right?
Mrs. Chu?
It's not funny.
What's going on?
Ms. Chu, come to your senses.
Ms. Chu.
You can't do that.
It's a joke, right?
you got me through
please come to your senses already.
I'm here
I'm near Please come to your senses.
Enough.
Save her.
I cannot raise the dead.
Why not? I know you can!
Rescue her immediately.
Please save her.
I'll sign a contract or whatever you want
so please
Please save her.
Only this time.
Ms. Chu!
You can't do that.
Come to your senses!
Ms. Chu!
Please save her.
With Ms. To suddenly
the spark of life is gone.
She must be in shock.
She was very close to the head.
Go comfort her?
Futile attempts to console
will only cause her more pain.
Try not to show emotion.
it's better now
what can you do for her
She was always like that.
That's you.
You don't even cry.
I don't deserve to cry.
They died because of me.
So what, it was my birthday?
I shouldn't have rushed them.
Do you consider yourself God?
How can someone die because of you?
you feel sorry for yourself
if you think so, don't you?
You are nothing more than dust
circling in the air.
Dust
cannot outweigh the scales.
That's it.
Well done.
Mom Dad
I miss you.
To Hee.
To Hee
I called you many times
but you didn't answer
Ms. Chu did not like to take pictures.
She said that they never
did not match her beauty.
I think this one is beautiful.
But she is nothing compared to her.
She looks empty with that smile.
Funeral portraits reflect what
bereaved relatives want to remember the deceased.
It still seems like a joke.
It seems that she is about to appear
and shouts: "Surprise, little rascal!"
Then she laughs.
It would really be more like her.
She was so eccentric.
I thought her last moments
will also be special.
But a heart attack?
did you just come
Yes, Aunt Jung Suk, it seems
ordered to create an audit team
before death
It's on hold now
but I had to take care of the papers.
The audit team?
Who delayed it?
The council passed an immediate resolution.
Haven't you heard about it?
Now is not the time for an audit.
Take a look.
Everyone tries to flatter Sook Min.
Is this the Joseon Dynasty or what?
It doesn't matter that he is the eldest son.
Mom never loved Suk Min.
She even sent him behind bars
for driving while intoxicated.
I have a feeling
that mom would make an unexpected choice.
Don't you agree?
Yes. She was truly unique.
Seok Hoon, come over for a minute.
It seems that there has always been between you
a special bond.
The camaraderie of outsiders, right?
We're just together
were students abroad.
But don't kid yourself, To Hee.
Seok Hoon doesn't come from the same background as you.
He comes from the Chu family,
and you are from a poor family
whose members worked with mechanisms
and the hair of others.
nice
you think
Is this the Joseon Dynasty or what?
Are you still snapping at me?
Your mother is gone, there is no one to protect you.
It's time to drink if you don't want to
so that everyone can see who you really are.
I never can
survive a funeral without alcohol.
All in black.
It's terrible.
I put up with far worse things
completely sober.
Mom was always angry.
I think that's why...
you got along with her.
Greetings, Isabelle.
Greetings, long time no see.
I am so glad to see you.
Heard a lot about you from the head Noh.
Of course.
It's still too early to call me that.
Greetings, madam.
Please don't say that.
I'm afraid that's a bit inappropriate.
I think so too.
There are also more and more women heads.
You are right.
Austin!
Justin!
- Austin!
- Boys are like that.
Justin!
So it was a party, not a funeral?
SECURITY
CAMERAS CONTROL ROOM
FOR EMPLOYEES ONLY
The seasons are different under and above the ground.
Underground, spring begins in October.
Although winter is cold on earth,
the buds make their way underground.
So tell yourself that when it's hard.
"Spring is about to bloom in me."
Why is it about Mother Nature?
It doesn't look like you.
Found something.
Just play along, you bastard.
Choose a character and be consistent.
Are you mother nature or lady black mouth?
I'm a black-faced lady, so what?
Just put it here.
God, the water is flowing!
- Oh, just go away.
- What's wrong?
Away!
- You can't spray like that!
- Okay, of course!
I thought there was no one here.
do you want
Mrs. Chu hates the smell of cigarettes.
Grandmother? But she died.
Now everything belongs to my dad
and will soon become mine.
I prefer the smell of cigarettes
and not the smell of an old woman.
I said, Ms. Chu
hates the smell of cigarettes.
Today I will forgive it.
Because today
happy day
I will not forgive it.
I wasn't the only one who wanted to get out of there.
Can I join?
who are you
I am inseparable from Mrs. To To Hee.
But get me right.
I'm not her ex
and definitely not her boyfriend.
- Are you her bodyguard?
- No.
Just finished work.
Would you like a sip?
You can't hide your upbringing.
You are a perfect couple.
What the hell?
Would you like a sip?
Ms. Chu
secluded here
when she felt sad.
I never understood that in her...
until this moment
The greenhouse protected not only her plants,
and Mrs. Chu herself.
She realized…
that her children will be happy
her death
Her prediction came true.
Probably, that's why she was always so evil.
She was lonely all her life
until the last moment.
my heart is breaking
because I couldn't say goodbye to her.
You know why people
do they wear black to funerals?
In order not to allow
souls of the deceased to recognize them and follow them.
That's why
they hide behind black clothes.
Then I'm wearing the wrong color today.
Mrs. Chu must still be so lonely today.
She cannot recognize anyone
at his own funeral.
Now she can recognize you.
What's the point?
I wouldn't know even if I did
she came to see
Just give it a chance.
Thank you Ms. Chu,
that found me
And 17 years ago, and now.
Thanks to you
I could behave as much as I wanted
like a child of the devil.
If we ever have a second chance...
let's fight...
even harder
and let's love each other even more.
A little Are you at a fashion show?
You have to stand out, right?
Aren't we all here like a burnt family?
Who gave her the right to be here?
The detective has information for all of us.
What could it be?
Glad to see you all.
Sorry, it didn't work out.
Whatever it is, let's finish quickly.
It is rude of us to leave guests alone.
Of course, sir.
Detective Lee.
There are too many documents to review.
Did the deceased drink painkillers often?
Yes, she had a knee problem.
The medicine she drank on the day of her death...
it was diclofenac.
Hold on. This is impossible.
She never drank it
because she was allergic to it.
But it is confirmed that before death
she drank exactly diclofenac.
I tell you this
because the pill did not match the label.
You say that mother is dead
due to medical negligence?
We thought it was just a heart attack.
Didn't Director Choi prescribe her medicine?
How could this happen?
We will consider all options,
therefore, let's not rush to conclusions.
Mr Cha and the audit team.
For now, I can only tell you,
what can she do to you
head of "Mire Group".
IBUPROFEN
Probably Mr Cha
had evidence of someone's crime.
And this person killed Ms. Chu,
so that she does not dig up anything.
Medical negligence sounds bad.
Especially considering that
that "Mire Group" is in a crisis situation.
We will only give reason for rumours.
One thought about what people will say
gives me a headache
Everyone will eagerly make up stories.
They think we, chaebols,
sold their souls to the devil or something.
How far have our stocks fallen?
They cannot be allowed to fall further.
First, who knew
that the deceased had an allergy
on diclofenac?
Her doctor...
as well as everyone present.
Let's announce that it was a heart attack.
That's a good idea.
We cannot allow rumours
right before imitation.
And again -
we won't bring mom back to life
if we reveal the truth.
I will speak to the Commissioner General.
Make sure it stays a secret.
Where is lawyer Jeon?
He is waiting outside.
Will the will be read outside?
We want it to be official.
Of course, there is no point in waiting.
Detective Puck.
Ms. Chu was killed.
It wasn't a heart attack
or medical negligence.
It was murder.
I know why Madame Chu was killed
and why they can kill me.
are you drunk
Why are you making a scene?
Which one of you did it?
You? Are you?
Does…
are you all involved?
Get her out of here.
Move away if you don't want to get hurt.
To Hee, what is it?
What's going on?
Let's start.
Ms To To Hee is required to be present.
Mrs. Choo Jeong-suk left a will,
describing your assets,
including shares and convertible bonds,
along with the deferred condition.
Condition?
Her will is as follows.
"I bequeath all real estate,
including an estate in Hannam-ton
and cash as a donation
"Khansaran Charitable Foundation".
I also bequeath
management rights of "Mire Group",
all shares and subsidiaries
designated heir".
Who is this "designated heir"?
"The designated heir
is the general director of "Mire Nutrition"
To To Hee."
What just happened?
As expected from her.
Is this a surprise party?
"Inheritance
depends on marriage registration
To To Hee for one year
after the death of the heiress, Choo Jung-suk.
If this condition is not met,
her share will pass
"Khansaran Charitable Foundation".
To To Hee…
will be our head?
The deceased also wrote letters
members of her family,
as this news could you
quite shocking.
Let me take a look.
I'm sure there's more.
My mother would do that to me.
"Money has corrupted you all.
Every man in your life…”
Seriously?
What is written there?
You don't want to know that.
Ms. Chu.
What the hell is this?
She made a choice
after serious hesitation.
TO TO HI
You!
what did you do
What the hell did you do?
calm down Get yourself together!
You wouldn't agree, would you?
The only way to stop me is
kill me
To Hee
Wait and see, Ms. Chu.
I promise, I will reveal the truth,
even if you have to
join forces with the demon.
Mr. Jeong Koo Won.
marry me
MY BELOVED DEMON
I think you better not get into it.
I have to find out who is behind this.
To do this, I need to create an audit group.
Between Mrs. To and Mr. Jeong.
Their communication expresses,
that there is physical intimacy between them.
I don't want them to go out alone
and got into trouble.
So let me continue
hold your wrist
And so they suspect that we are dating.
A wonderful day, young Mr. Yi Sun.
Young sir!
My memories are starting to come back.
There is nothing better,
than holding handsin secret
under the table at the team lunch.
In secret physical touch
there is something so wonderful.
I like To To Hee.
Translation of subtitles: Daria Hochel